[{"answer": " I love watching the Olympics, dont you", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " I do.  I love sports and its so cool to see athletes from all over the worl", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 13, "question": " I love watching the Olympics, dont you", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " I could sit here all day and watch them", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 17, "question": " I do.  I love sports and its so cool to see athletes from all over the worl", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " We almost have been", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 18, "question": " I could sit here all day and watch them", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " We should try to get tickets for the next Olympic Games.  Wouldnt that b", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 19, "question": " We almost have been", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " It would be so cool.  Where are the next Games going to be", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 23, "question": " We should try to get tickets for the next Olympic Games.  Wouldnt that b", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " In 2010 theyre going to be in Vancouver, Canada, in 2012 its London, England", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 24, "question": " It would be so cool.  Where are the next Games going to be", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " They already have the cities chosen so far in advance", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 28, "question": " In 2010 theyre going to be in Vancouver, Canada, in 2012 its London, England", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Yep.  They choose the cities seven years in advance", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 29, "question": " They already have the cities chosen so far in advance", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Wow.  Itd be cool to go to China and see the Games.  London would b", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Yep.  They choose the cities seven years in advance", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " There is a group called the International Olympic Committee, or the IOC.  The", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Wow.  Itd be cool to go to China and see the Games.  London would b", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " How are countries nominated", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 41, "question": " There is a group called the International Olympic Committee, or the IOC.  The", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Im not exactly sure, but I think a countrys National Olympic Committee ca", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 42, "question": " How are countries nominated", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " There must be a lot of rules to follow", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Im not exactly sure, but I think a countrys National Olympic Committee ca", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Yeah, there are.  When they apply, countries have to fill out a questionnaire an", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 47, "question": " There must be a lot of rules to follow", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " What kind of stuff do they look for when choosing candidate cities", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Yeah, there are.  When they apply, countries have to fill out a questionnaire an", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " I think its things like government support, public opinion, security, venues", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 52, "question": " What kind of stuff do they look for when choosing candidate cities", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " That makes sense.  I guess they have to make sure that the selected city ca", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 56, "question": " I think its things like government support, public opinion, security, venues", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Right", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 60, "question": " That makes sense.  I guess they have to make sure that the selected city ca", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Just imagine how many hotel rooms they need", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Right", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " I know", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Just imagine how many hotel rooms they need", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " So, what happens after they choose the candidate cities", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 63, "question": " I know", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " The cities have to submit more information to the IOC, and the IOC visits th", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 64, "question": " So, what happens after they choose the candidate cities", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Right.  I guess they have to make sure theyre not lying and that they hav", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 68, "question": " The cities have to submit more information to the IOC, and the IOC visits th", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Yeah.  Then, the committee votes on what city should host the Olympics", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Right.  I guess they have to make sure theyre not lying and that they hav", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Wouldnt it be awesome if the Olympics were here in our city", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Yeah.  Then, the committee votes on what city should host the Olympics", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " I dont think they ever would be.  Our town is too small.  We couldnt hos", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Wouldnt it be awesome if the Olympics were here in our city", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " I know.  I guess youre right.  I just wish we could go and see the Olympics", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 81, "question": " I dont think they ever would be.  Our town is too small.  We couldnt hos", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " I think its hard to get tickets to the Olympics if youre not a citizen of the countr", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 82, "question": " I know.  I guess youre right.  I just wish we could go and see the Olympics", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " Oh.  I guess it would be too expensive for us to travel to China, anyways.  I", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 87, "question": " I think its hard to get tickets to the Olympics if youre not a citizen of the countr", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " Yeah, we might just have to keep watching the Olympics on TV", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 91, "question": " Oh.  I guess it would be too expensive for us to travel to China, anyways.  I", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": " I guess so.  Its fun to watch them here too", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Yeah, we might just have to keep watching the Olympics on TV", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Lets get some more snacks, and we can be couch potatoes for the rest of th", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 93, "question": " I guess so.  Its fun to watch them here too", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " Sounds good to me", "docId": "08-10", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Lets get some more snacks, and we can be couch potatoes for the rest of th", "qSentId": 96}]
